天呐，希望我衣服也能那样合身，
God, I wish my clothes fit like that,
她身体曲线就像个活的美元符号$
her curves look like a dollar sign came to life, man
好烦啊，我的提臀裤老是扭啊扭的
Oh God, my spanx are writhing up
她的头发太好看了吧？
How is her hair such goals?
她真是个长发公主
She's actually Rapunzel
这高跟鞋也太酷了，希望我也能穿上
Those pumps are fire, I wish I could walk
in heels like her, she came in here
这样的鞋子走路。她进来时
looking like Naomi Campbell walk, Naomi Campbell walk,
看起来像娜奥米·坎贝尔，娜奥米·坎贝尔走猫步，
my ankles would snap
要是我的话脚踝就断了
Oh come on, man, her eyebrows are the literal
厉害，她的眉毛就是字面意思
fleek的定义，我敢说，这是
definition of fleek, and I bet those are
她真正的睫毛。
her real lashes too.
Oh, her eyeballs are so protected.
哦，她的眼睛保养的真好。
Oh this sucks, I'm in an elevator with two Malibu Barbies.
噢，真糟糕，我和两个马里布芭比娃娃一起在电梯里。
Are you guys going down?
你们要下去吗？
下来，是的。
Down, yeah, yeah.
抱歉，我往上去。
Ah, sorry, I'm going up.
我是说他很可爱，但那些甜甜圈更吸引人。
I mean he was cute but, those donuts though.
同感，对于釉面甜甜圈，我们可以
I know, for a glazed doughnut, we can take
high一会儿了。
a little ride up for a second.
他可以把甜甜圈留给我们，
I mean, leave the glazed doughnuts with us,
然后去走楼梯。
you can take the stairs.
BT配靓女，这身装扮太给力了。
BT dubs girl, this outfit is everything.
哦，谢谢！
Oh thanks!
同样你的睫毛，它们真翘，我说真的。
And your lashes, I mean they're popping, for real.
哦，谢谢。
Oh thanks.
真的，真心实意，
I mean, that's true and all,
但是我还在想那些甜甜圈。
but I'm still thinking about those doughnuts.
噢，天哪，会抓重点。
Oh my God, priorities on fleek.
我们去找那些甜甜圈。
Let's go find those doughnuts.
为什么我们不刚进电梯就开始说话？
Why didn't we just start talking when we got into the elevator?
不然我们五分钟之前就是好朋友了。
We could have been best friends like five minutes ago.
说到好友，我要借你的鞋子穿穿，
Speaking of which, girl, imma have to borrow those shoes,
还有脚踝护具。
and an ankle brace.